It’s my pleasure to welcome Ms. Ruth Jones
the sales manager for RMT Company
She is going to present their new Bluetooth speaker
I am sure you all will find her presentation interesting
Thank you so much
It’s a privilege to be here
On behalf of SK Tech, I’d like to welcome you
This is Mark Spencer
the marketing manager at MT Inc
He is here to present their new series of health apps
Let’s give him our full attention
I appreciate your warm welcome
Thank you for giving me this opportunity
Good morning, ladies and gentlemen
It’s a pleasure to welcome
all of you to today’s meeting
Welcome. I’m delighted that
so many of you could make it today
Thank you all for taking time
out of your busy schedules to attend this meeting
My name is Linda Johnson
and I am the human resources manager for RM Company
For those of you who don’t know me
I’m Eric Carson, sales analyst from YT Inc
Let me just start by introducing myself
I am Albert Kao
an electronics engineer from QE Tech
Introducing your work responsibilities
I am responsible for recruiting
hiring and training employees
I’m in charge of the sales department
at our Chicago office
I manage the engineering division of the company